<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Analyst Portfolio on Murad Farhan</title>
    <link>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Analyst Portfolio on Murad Farhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2:Profiling and Analyzing the Yelp Dataset With SQL</title>
      <link>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I will be using a dataset from a US-based organization called Yelp, which provides a platform for users to provide reviews and rate their interactions with a variety of organizations – businesses, restaurants, health clubs, hospitals, local governmental offices, charitable organizations, etc. Yelp has made a portion of this data available for personal, educational, and academic purposes.
I will perform profile and better understand the data in the first part of the case study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project I: Cyclistic bike-share With R</title>
      <link>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this case study, I will perform data analysis for a fictional bike-share called Cyclistic.In 2016, Cyclistic launched a successful bike-share offering. Since then, the program has grown to a fleet of 5,824 bicycles that are geotracked and locked into a network of 692 stations across Chicago. The bikes can be unlocked from one station and returned to any other station in the system anytime.Customers who purchase single-ride or full-day passes are referred to as casual riders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Murad Ahmed Farhan (1997)   Data for me is the tool that answer the questions in our minds and guides us for solutions. I am a thorough and meticulous Data Analyst passionate about helping businesses succeed. Experienced in interpreting and analyzing data to drive growth for a business. Possessing strong technical skills rooted in substantial training as an data analysis to turn over the raw data to visual data, plot, figure, and/or presentation by analyzing the data which will help stakeholders to make decisions and know the current status of the data analyzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://da-murad.github.io/Murad-Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these platforms and social media
   Platform: URL     Kaggel: https://www.kaggle.com/muradfarhan   GitHub: https://github.com/DA-MURAD   Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/murad-farhan-455a79220/   Public.Tableau: https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/murad.ahmed.abdullah.farhan    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>